LEVAN REVAZASHVILI

.NET DEVELOPER ♥ TBILISI, GEORGIA ६ (+995) 598 120 475

• DETAILS •

Tbilisi Georgia (+995) 598 120 475 levanrevazashvili@gmail.com

• LINKS •

LinkedIn

Github

• SKILLS •

C#.NET

ASP.NET Core Web API

ASP.NET Core MVC

Blazor

Docker

GraphQL

REST

SOAP

PostgreSQL

MSSQL

Redis

RabbitMQ

AWS

Azure

PROFILE

.Net Developer with 3+ years of experience in developing and implementing complex software applications. Experienced with the latest cutting edge development tools and procedures. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Senior .Net Developer at Bank of Georgia

October 2021 — Present

- Worked on business internet and mobile banking applications.
- Developed public integration API for accounting or other business application.
- Maintained existing functionality, developed new features and provided bug fixes.
- Analyzed and optimized the application's performance.
- · Migrating legacy code to latest technologies.
- Worked as solution architect for mobile banking team.
- · Created technical documentation.

Middle .Net Developer at Liberty Bank

October 2020 — October 2021

- Developed online payment services for CRM, mobile and internet bank, pay box and other internal channels.
- Communicated with stakeholders, analyzing requirements and provided relevant solutions.
- Developed database functions, procedures and database objects.
- · Supported websites built with ASP.NET Web Forms technology.
- Integrated message brokers such as RabbitMQ to implement asynchronous payment process.

Middle .Net Developer at Proway

January 2021 — September 2021

- Developed survey website with .Net 5 and PostgreSQL.
- Implemented CMS with PiranhaCms library in ASP.NET Core MVC.
- Participated in front-end development process using Blazor.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science, Tbilisi State University, Tbilisi

September 2019 — Present